<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>James Wang on 沈潔</title>
    <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/tags/james-wang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in James Wang on 沈潔</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/tags/james-wang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Should Help Taiwan On the Diplomatic Front</title>
      <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2005-07-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2005-07-23/</guid>
      <description>Taipei Times
U.S. Should Help Taiwan On the Diplomatic Front
by James Wang Although the U.S. government continues to complain about the lack of transparency in China&amp;rsquo;s military modernizaton, it is crystal clear that China&amp;rsquo;s militray build-up poses a seriuos threat to the security of Taiwan and, in the long terms, the U.S. forces in the area.
China has arrogantly repeated its threats and intimidations through words and deeeds. And the annual report to the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Kissinger Forgets What He said</title>
      <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2005-06-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2005-06-27/</guid>
      <description>Taipei Times
Henry Kissinger Forgets What He said by James Wang
Dr. Henry A. Kissinger, former U.S. secretary of state, is a man known for his craftiness in the nuance of diplomatic language. But, for some reasons, his grips of the skill seems beginning to rust, as it showed in his article, China: Containment Won&amp;rsquo;t Work, published in the Washington Post on June 13, 2005.
Dr. Kissinger stated in that article that &amp;ldquo;almost all countries &amp;ndash; and all major ones &amp;ndash; have recognized China&amp;rsquo;s claim that Taiwan is part of China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peng Ming-min Case as seen in American Diplomatic Files</title>
      <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2004-10-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2004-10-14/</guid>
      <description>Taiwan News
Peng Ming-min Case as seen in American Diplomatic Files by James Wang
Forty years ago, Gimo Chiang Kai-shek was still enthusiastically shouting slogans of counter-attack and regaining control over Chinese mainland. But outsiders knew better. The situations, domestic and international, were getting worse. His dream of returning to Chinese mainland as liberator was rapidly fading away.
Early in 1964, Gen. de Gaulle decided to abandon Gimo Chiang and recognize Mao&amp;rsquo;s regime as representative of China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Triangular Relations Become History</title>
      <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2002-06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2002-06-07/</guid>
      <description>Taipei Times
The Triangular Relations Become History By James Wang
Without a fanafre,the United States and Russia reached a three-page long nuclear arms reduction treaty, and Russia becomes a partner of NATO, indicating its further integration with the West.
After a bitter collapse in the early 1990&amp;rsquo;s, Russia finally finds its peace with itself and its former enemies.
Now we can see a Russia that cooperates with the United States and other major powers to promote peace and stability around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Peace Treaty Revisited</title>
      <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2002-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2002-05-02/</guid>
      <description>For Taipei Times
San Francisco Peace Treaty Revisited by James Wang
When former president Lee Teng-hui embraced the idea that &amp;ldquo;sovereignty resides in the people,&amp;rdquo; his statement didn&amp;rsquo;t raise many eyebrows. Almost everyone took it for granted because it is the ABC&amp;rsquo;s of Democarcy and it was stipulated in Article 2 of the Constitution.
And, when George W. Bush, President of the United States, insisted that the resolution of the disputes between Taiwan and the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of Chinashould have the consent of the people of Taiwan, he seemed also talking along the line of Democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Lien&#39;s Political Judgment In Question</title>
      <link>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2002-04-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuenyangwang.github.io/shenjiah/posts/2002-04-22/</guid>
      <description>For Taipei Times
Mr. Lien&amp;rsquo;s Political Judgment In Question by James Wang
At a time when the Middle east was in crisis, the Bush Administration was under fire for its inaction in seeking for peace, and the situation in the Taiwan Strait was relatively quiet, it is hard to explain why Mr. Lien Chan, Chairman of the KMT, took a trip to Washington, D.C.
Mr. Lien&amp;rsquo;s visit generated a brief report in the Washington Times, which lead the story by quoting Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>